aarkcollective.com 2018-12-21

# AÃRK Collective | Support

AÃRK Collective Pty Ltd

St Kilda Rd  
Melbourne, VIC 3004  
Australia 

ABN: 93 143 876 066  
ACN: 143 876 066 

All purchases from aarkcollective.com are entitled to a 14-day money back guarantee. If you are not happy with your purchase for any reason, you can return your watch to us within the first 14 days following your delivery date and we will offer you a full refund or exchange. Returns will only be accepted if the item is in new, unused and re-sellable condition, and with the original packaging. Shipping charges on returned merchandise are at the customer's expense. Refunds for returned merchandise will be made within 2 weeks of the return of the product, to the original purchaser’s credit card. Note that additional duties and/or taxes will not be refunded. Neither will shipping costs.

To make a return, please contact us by email at [service@aarkcollective.com](mailto:service@prismist.com) to notify us of the reason of your return. Please include your full name and order number as reference. Upon receipt of your email we will send you a Returns Authorisation email including a Returns Form and Returns Code.

Faulty products that have been purchased from aarkcollective.com can be replaced or refunded within 14 days after delivery. For products that become faulty after the 14 days guarantee or have been purchased from an authorised reseller, we offer a 2 year limited warranty. Please refer to our warranty section for more information.

AÃRK Collective ships worldwide and all shipping charges are included in the price stated on the website. Australian orders are shipped for FREE using Australia Express Post, which provides an overnight service to most major cities, and a two-day service for the rest of the country. All International orders are shipped by UPS, DHL, FedEx or Australia Post with an option for standard shipping or express shipping. A tracking number will be sent to you via email once your order has been dispatched so you can track your item, and a signature will be required upon delivery.

Once payment has been received we usually dispatch your order within 24 hours. Delivery times vary depending on the country and Customs issues and are therefore only indicative. You may also be responsible for import duties and taxes on your international order. Unfortunately, we have no control over these charges or delays and cannot predict what they may be. We suggest that you contact your local Customs office for additional information. 

We accept online payments by Visa, MasterCard, American Express or Pay Pal. When purchasing from AÃRK Collective your financial details are passed through a secure server using the latest 128-bit SSL (secure socket layer) encryption technology. Credit card details are never stored on the aarkcollective.com website in any way, and are passed on directly to our Payment Gateway (ANZ eGate) for authorisation and authentication.

We respect the privacy of everyone who visits this site. Please read our Privacy Policy so that you have an understanding of how we collect and use the personal information that you provide to us.

 **Privacy Policy  
** _  
Personal Information_  
We protect your personal details and do not sell or give them to other parties. The information that is collected by AÃRK is used for ordering and delivery only. Users who have opted (subscribe) to receive newsletter emails from AÃRK Collective about product updates, specials and news may unsubscribe at any time.

 _Third Party Tracking Tools  
_ The AÃRK Collective website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies to learn more about the way you interact with our content and more importantly to help us improve your user experience when visiting our site.

Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device which have the ability to store certain information that identifies:  
—Your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address  
—The type of browser you use and any additional browser software you have installed  
—User behaviour (for web analysis services and third party tracking tools such as targeted advertising)

A cookie does not have the ability to collect personally identifiable information about you. Any personal information provided to us which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained (such as your home address and home telephone number for example) will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected.

By accessing or using this website you acknowledge and agree to be bound by this privacy notice.

You can choose to reject or block the cookies set by this website or any third party suppliers by changing your browser settings – see the Help function within your browser for clarification. Additionally, for further information on how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising please visit the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) [website](http://www.aboutads.info/).

 _Changes to the Privacy Policy  
_ AÃRK Collective reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review this page frequently as any changes will be outlined here.

AÃRK watches are warranted to the original owner for two years from the date of purchase. The warranty covers any and all parts of the watch that may need repair due to defects in materials or workmanship under normal use. AÃRK Collective's obligations hereunder are limited to repair or replacement at its option. The warranty excludes the battery, strap and excessive wear or damage to the case or crystal. AÃRK watches is not liable for any consequential or incidental damages, and any recovery may not exceed the amount paid for the timepiece. Any claim made under the above warranties directly with AÃRK will involve you returning the defective goods to us, at your expense. AÃRK will cover the cost of returning the repaired or replacement product to you. When returning the product please include a copy of the warranty form and also proof of purchase.

Products displayed on this website are available while stocks permit and can be removed without any prior notice. The pricing and descriptions of products can also be amended at any point without notice being given. We aim to display the colours of our products as accurately as possible, however as resolution, print methods and screen settings can affect how an item is displayed, the accuracy of colours cannot be guaranteed. 

We reserve the right to refuse to supply products to any individual or company. AÃRK is a Trade Mark of AÃRK Collective Pty Ltd, registered Company of Australia at 94 / 604 St Kilda Rd, Melbourne VIC Australia, ACN number 986 5344 70. All associated Intellectual property, including text, product names and descriptions, imagery, brochures and web site design remain the property of AÃRK Collective Pty Ltd and cannot be reproduced without prior written consent. These Terms and Conditions may be updated at any time.
